https://www.invitationsbydawn.com/content/privacy-security/

Shop by Theme
Back Elegant Invitations Minimalist Invitations Rustic Invitations Floral Invitations Classic Invitations Vintage Invitations Traditional Invitations Destination Invitations Modern Invitations Fall Invitations
Shop by Collection
Back The Love Blooms Collection The Naturally Ever After Collection The Autumn Romance Collection The Golden Glow Collection
Shop Value Invitations
Back Seal and Send™ Invitations 3 for 1 Invitations Petite Wedding Invitations
Shop By Type
Back Ribbon Invitations Luxury Invitations Laser Cut Invitations Photo Invitations Foil Stamped Invitations Letterpress Invitations Pocket Invitations Vellum Invitations
Shop DIY
Back Design Your Own Wedding Invitations Wedding Envelopes Wedding Envelope Seals and Embossers Personalized Stamps Wedding Invitation Wraps Wedding Invitation Pockets Belly Bands for Invitations Wedding Envelope Liners
Save The Dates
Back Shop All Save the Dates
Photo Save the Dates Holiday Save the Dates Magnet Save the Dates Foil Stamped Save the Dates Puzzle Save the Dates Postcard Save the Dates
Ceremony & Reception Decor
Back Shop Ceremony Decor
Back Wedding Programs Wedding Personalized Yard Signs Personalized Stamps Wedding Ceremony Decorations
Shop Reception Decor
Back Wedding Napkins Wedding Place Cards Wedding Menu Cards Wedding Favors Candy Bags Wedding Reception Decorations
Bridal Shower & Celebrations
Back Shop All Bridal Shower
Wedding Celebrations
Back Rehearsal Dinner Invitations Anniversary Party Invitations Vow Renewal Invitations
Thank You Notes & More
Back Shop All Thank You Notes
Shop by Theme
Back Elegant Thank You Cards Modern Thank You Cards Rustic Thank You Cards Vintage Thank You Cards
More Stationery
Back Wedding Response Cards Wedding Envelopes Wedding Reception and Information Cards Wedding Envelope Seals and Embossers Personalized Stamps
E-MAIL SIGN UP FREE SAMPLES
HOME
TODAY'S DEALS
FREE SAMPLES
Wedding Invitations
Back Shop All Wedding Invitations
Shop by Theme
Back Elegant Invitations Minimalist Invitations Rustic Invitations Floral Invitations Classic Invitations Vintage Invitations Traditional Invitations Destination Invitations Modern Invitations Fall Invitations
Shop by Collection
Back The Love Blooms Collection The Naturally Ever After Collection The Autumn Romance Collection The Golden Glow Collection
Shop Value Invitations
Back Seal and Send™ Invitations 3 for 1 Invitations Petite Wedding Invitations
Shop By Type
Back Ribbon Invitations Luxury Invitations Laser Cut Invitations Photo Invitations Foil Stamped Invitations Letterpress Invitations Pocket Invitations Vellum Invitations
Shop DIY
Back Design Your Own Wedding Invitations Wedding Envelopes Wedding Envelope Seals and Embossers Personalized Stamps Wedding Invitation Wraps Wedding Invitation Pockets Belly Bands for Invitations Wedding Envelope Liners
Save The Dates
Back Shop All Save the Dates
Photo Save the Dates Holiday Save the Dates Magnet Save the Dates Foil Stamped Save the Dates Puzzle Save the Dates Postcard Save the Dates
Ceremony & Reception Decor
Back Shop Ceremony Decor
Back Wedding Programs Wedding Personalized Yard Signs Personalized Stamps Wedding Ceremony Decorations
Shop Reception Decor
Back Wedding Napkins Wedding Place Cards Wedding Menu Cards Wedding Favors Candy Bags Wedding Reception Decorations
Bridal Shower & Celebrations
Back Shop All Bridal Shower
Wedding Celebrations
Back Rehearsal Dinner Invitations Anniversary Party Invitations Vow Renewal Invitations
Thank You Notes & More
Back Shop All Thank You Notes
Shop by Theme
Back Elegant Thank You Cards Modern Thank You Cards Rustic Thank You Cards Vintage Thank You Cards
More Stationery
Back Wedding Response Cards Wedding Envelopes Wedding Reception and Information Cards Wedding Envelope Seals and Embossers Personalized Stamps
E-MAIL SIGN UP
Home Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Last Updated: January 1, 2020 At www.invitationsbydawn.com, we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy.
The purpose of this privacy notice is to let you know what kind of information we collect, how we use it, with whom it may be shared, what choices you have regarding our use of your information, and how you may review and change some of the data you provide to us. For your benefit, we've provided an Overview of our privacy practices and the Full Privacy Notice below.
Our practices comply with applicable U.S. laws and requirements. We are located in the United States and this is an U.S.-based website.
By using this site, you agree to the transfer of your personal information to or within the United States.
If you are located within the European Union and are transmitting personal data on this website please review the “GDPR Support” section below. If you are a California Resident, please see our "Privacy Notice for California Residents" section below. As we continue to develop our website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this policy likely will change.
When we change it, we will post the change(s) on our website.
If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you. You can determine when this version of the privacy notice was adopted by referring to the “Effective Date” below.
If you have questions about our privacy notice, please contact us via email at contact@invitationsbydawn.com. Privacy Overview This is a summary of how we may collect, use and transmit information about you. It is a general overview only, and must be read in conjunction with Full Privacy Notice below. How we collect information and what information we collect
Information You Provide to Us: we collect personally-identifiable information, including name, title, company, address, email address, phone numbers, etc. when and if you voluntarily provide it to us. Information You Collect Automatically: our servers also collect the IP addresses of visitors to our site.
Information We Receive from Other Sources: We may use cookies on our websites; for complete information please review the Full Privacy Notice below.
How we may use your information
To facilitate customer service or to enable us to contact you if you request information.
To target valuable marketing and advertising offers.
To perform research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us when making a purchase, during a promotion, from surveys and from our server log files.
To may match user information with third party data to help us better understand our customers (customer profiling).
Who collects your information When visiting this site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Invitations by Dawn, our subsidiaries, affiliates and related companies, our service providers and business partners.
Do we share information
We may share the information you provide with our subsidiaries and related companies. In addition, we may share your information with third parties as set forth in the Full Privacy Notice. Third Party websites Our website may contain various links to third-party websites. We are providing these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by us, or any association with its operators, or with any of its products or services. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use.
Privacy Help Please review the Full Privacy Notice below. If you have questions about our policy, please contact us in writing at contact@invitationsbydawn.com. GDPR Support The following provision applies if the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies to the particular transaction and if you are a data subject, as defined by the GDPR, within the European Economic Area.
We are based in the United States and any personal data collected from this website will be transferred and processed within the U.S. If you do not agree to this, do not provide us with personal data.
Data Controller: Invitations by Dawn Data Subject Rights to Personal Information
to access your information and to receive information about its use to have your information corrected and/or completed to have your information deleted to restrict the use of your information to receive your information in a portable format to object to the use of your information to withdraw your consent to the use of your information to complain to a supervisory authority
Your rights as a data subject may be subject to certain limitations and restrictions. You may exercise your rights as a data subject by contacting us in writing at gdprnotices@invitationsbydawn.com.
When you make a request, we may require certain documentation in order to be able to verify your identity before we are able process your request. Your cooperation is necessary to exercise your rights under the GDPR.
Sensitive personal information: we do not knowingly or intentionally collect what is commonly referred to as ‘sensitive personal information', as defined by the GDPR. Please do not submit sensitive personal information about you to us.
Full Privacy Notice 1. When do we collect information We collect personally-identifiable information when you provide it to us. In addition, our website servers collect the IP addresses of visitors to our websites. In addition, we might receive personal data and other online and offline information from our business partners who share it with us. We will use such information in accordance with applicable laws and this Privacy Notice. 2. What information do we collect The personal information we collect might include your name, title, company, address, email address, phone numbers, etc. If you make a purchase on our site, your credit card number and related information will be collected. We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive from you offline. We may also receive information about you from other sources, including, for example, address update services. Finally, we also collect information using cookies and web beacons to collect information such as your IP address, browser type, the time and length of your visit, the pages of the site you visit and other clickstream data. Additional information about cookies is located below. 3. How we may use your information We may use or disclose the personal information we collect for one or more of the following business purposes:
To fulfill or meet the reason for which the information is provided.
To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
For example, we collect personal information to facilitate customer service or to enable us to contact you if you request information. To provide you with email alerts, and other offers and notices concerning our products or services, or events or news, that may be of interest to you, including targeted offers and ads through our website, third-party sites, and via email or text message (with your consent, where required by law).
To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collections. To improve our Website and present its contents to you.
For example, we use information provided by and/or collected from your use of the website to review site usage and operations, to address problems with the site, our business or our products and services, and to protect the security or integrity of the Website and our business.
Our servers may collect the domain names of visitors, as well as other information about your visit. This information is aggregated to measure number of visits, average time spent on a website, pages viewed, etc.
For testing, research, analysis and product development.
This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis to prevent identification of personal information relating to any one individual.
As necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our customers or others. To respond to law enforcement requests and as required by applicable law, court order, or governmental regulations. As described to you when collecting your personal information or as otherwise set forth in the California Consumer Protection Act of 2018 (“CCPA”). To evaluate or conduct a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us is among the assets transferred.
4. Reasons we share information We may transfer or otherwise disclose information collected from and about you for the following purposes:
To our service providers, suppliers and business associates, if the disclosure will enable them to fulfill your request for products or services on our site;
To our service providers and business associates, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us;
To certain affiliates that share common branding so that they may contact you with marketing offers of their own; To other companies, credit bureaus or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection;
As necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our site Terms of Use, of the law or of our rights or the rights of any third party;
To respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and If our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.
Any personal information or content that you voluntarily upload or submit for public posting to the site (for example, comments) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. It is in violation of the site's Terms of Use for you to post any content that requests personally identifiable information. 5. Who has access to your information When you are on our website and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with Invitations by Dawn, our subsidiaries and affiliates, and our service providers. We share your information as described in “Reasons we share information”, above. 6. Record Retention
We will retain your personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. We will also keep your personal data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services and to maintain a record of your transactions for financial reporting purposes. We retain archived copies of your information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. 7. Cookies & Similar Technologies
We, or third-party service providers acting on our behalf, may use cookies or web beacons on our site.
A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the site.
A web beacon is an electronic image used to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page.
We may use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information from you, including your IP address, browser type, the time and length of your visit, the pages of the site you visit and other clickstream data. This information may be used in order to:
recognize you when you return to the site; improve and personalize your experience on our site; provide you with customized advertising; and monitor site usage and analyze the behavior of site visitors.
You may decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. You also may be able to make some web beacons unusable by rejecting cookies. Check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. Most web browsers let you choose whether to accept cookies.
Most also let you delete cookies already set.
The choices available, and the mechanism used, will vary from browser to browser.
Such browser settings are typically found in the “options”, “tools” or “preferences” menu. You may also consult the browser’s “help” menu. For example:
Cookie settings in Internet Explorer
Cookie settings in Firefox
Cookie settings in Chrome
Cookie settings in Safari
There are online tools available for clearing all cookies left behind by the websites you have visited, such as www.allaboutcookies.org.
Usually, deletion of cookies will anonymize the information associated with the pixel and a website will not receive any further associated information. 8. Your Rights; Contact Us You can request to access, update, correct, and delete your information you provided to us by sending us an email at contact@invitationsbydawn.com. Keeping your personal data current helps ensure that we can respect your preferences. When you make a request, we may require certain documentation in order to be able to verify your identity before we are able process your request. Your cooperation is necessary to exercise your rights under this Privacy Notice. 9. Security of Personal Data
We have implemented an information security program that contains administrative, technical and physical controls that are designed to safeguard your personal data. While we use all reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your data submitted through our websites. 10. Third Parties This Privacy Notice only addresses the collection, processing and use (including disclosure) of information by us. This site may contain various links to third-party websites. These sites may provide additional information, goods, services and/or promotions. These sites are owned and operated independently of Invitations by Dawn, and have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. Any information you provide to these Websites will be governed under the terms of their privacy policy, if any. Invitations by Dawn has no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the independent actions or policies of these independent sites, and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites. 11. Additional Privacy Information Transfer of Data
We are based in the United States and any personal data collected from this website may be transferred to and processed within the U.S. The privacy protections and the rights of authorities to access your personal information in the U.S. may not be equivalent to those in your home country. By submitting your personal data, you're agreeing to this transfer, storing and/or processing of data.
Children's Privacy
This Website is not directed to or designed to solicit individuals under the age of 13. In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information, even in aggregate, about children under the age of 13. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe that we have any information from or about anyone under the age of 13, please contact us at contact@invitationsbydawn.com. California Do Not Track Disclosures
“Do Not Track” is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers. When a user turns on a Do Not Track signal in their browser, the browser sends a message to websites requesting that they do not track the user. For information about Do Not Track, please visit allaboutdnt.org. We have disclosed our collection practices herein, but at this time, we do not honor do-not track signals. Some of the third parties that we work with may honor such requests.
Privacy Notice For California Residents
This PRIVACY NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS supplements the information contained in the Privacy Notice of Invitations by Dawn, Inc. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “we,” “us,” or “our”) and applies solely to visitors, users, and others who reside in the State of California (“consumers” or “you”). For purposes of this section, any terms defined in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) have the same meaning when used in this notice.
Information We Collect
Category Examples Collected
A. Identifiers A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, or other similar identifiers. YES
B1. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)). Signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, passport number, driver's license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. NO
B2. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)). A name, Address, telephone number, credit card number. YES
C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law. Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). NO
D. Commercial information. Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. YES
E. Biometric information. Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data.
NO
F. Internet or other similar network activity. Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer's interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. YES
G. Geolocation data. Physical location or movements. NO
H. Sensory data. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information. NO
I. Professional or employment-related information. Current or past job history or performance evaluations. NO
J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)). Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records. NO
K. Inferences drawn from other personal information. Profile reflecting a person's preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. NO
We obtain the categories of personal information listed above from the following categories of sources:
Directly from you. For example, from users of our website when the user or their agent provides personal information to us. Indirectly from you.
For example, by observing your interactions on our website and by using cookies.
From third party business partners.
For example, address update services.
Sharing Personal Information
We may disclose your personal information to a third party for a business purpose.
When we disclose personal information for a business purpose, we enter a contract that describes the purpose and requires the recipient to both keep that personal information confidential and not use it for any purpose except performing the contract.
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose:
Category A:
Identifiers. Category B:
California Customer Records personal information categories. Category D:
Commercial Information Category F:
Internet or other similar network activity.
We will not collect additional categories of personal information or use the personal information we collected for materially different, unrelated, or incompatible purposes other than those set forth in our Privacy Notice without providing you notice.
We disclose your personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties:
Our affiliates. Service providers and business partners. Third parties to whom you or your agents authorize us to disclose your personal information in connection with products or services we provide to you.
In the preceding twelve (12) months, we have not sold any personal information of California resident consumers collected from the Website.
Your Rights and Choices The CCPA provides California residents with specific rights regarding their personal information. This section describes your CCPA rights and explains how to exercise those rights.
Access to Specific Information and Data Portability Rights
You have the right to request that we disclose certain information to you about our collection and use of your personal information over the past 12 months. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will disclose to you:
The categories of personal information we collected about you. The categories of sources for the personal information we collected about you. Our business or commercial purpose for collecting or selling that personal information. The categories of third parties with whom we share that personal information. The specific pieces of personal information we collected about you. The categories of personal information sold, the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, by category or categories of personal information for each third party to whom the personal information was sold; and The categories of personal information disclosed for a business purpose.
Deletion Request Rights
You have the right to request that we delete any of your personal information that we collected from you and retained, subject to certain exceptions. Once we receive and confirm your verifiable consumer request, we will delete (and direct our service providers to delete) your personal information from our records, unless an exception applies.
Exercising Your Rights
To exercise the rights described above, please submit a verifiable consumer request to us by either:
Calling toll free at 844-277-9138 or by submitting a request form. Only you or a person registered with the California Secretary of State that you authorize to act on your behalf, may make a verifiable consumer request related to your personal information. You may also make a verifiable consumer request on behalf of your minor child.
You may only make a verifiable consumer request for access or data portability twice within a 12-month period. The verifiable consumer request must:
Provide sufficient information that allows us to reasonably verify you are the person about whom we collected personal information or an authorized representative. Describe your request with sufficient detail that allows us to properly understand, evaluate, and respond to it.
We cannot respond to your request or provide you with personal information if we cannot verify your identity or authority to make the request and confirm the personal information relates to you.
Making a verifiable consumer request does not require you to create an account with us.
We will only use personal information provided in a verifiable consumer request to verify the requestor's identity or authority to make the request.
Response Timing and Format We try to respond to a verifiable consumer request within 45 days of its receipt.
If we require more time (up to 90 days), we will inform you of the reason and extension period in writing.
Any disclosures we provide will only cover the 12-month period preceding the verifiable consumer request's receipt.
The response we provide will also explain the reasons we cannot comply with a request, if applicable.
For data portability requests, we will select a format to provide your personal information that is readily useable and should allow you to transmit the information from one entity to another entity without hindrance. We do not charge a fee to process or respond to your verifiable consumer request unless it is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded.
If we determine that the request warrants a fee, we will tell you why we made that decision and provide you with a cost estimate before completing your request. Non-Discrimination We will not discriminate against you for exercising any of your CCPA rights. Unless permitted by the CCPA, we will not:
Deny you goods or services. Charge you different prices or rates for goods or services, including through granting discounts or other benefits, or imposing penalties. Provide you a different level or quality of goods or services. Suggest that you may receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services.
Changes to Our Privacy Notice We reserve the right to amend this privacy notice at our discretion and at any time. When we make changes to this privacy notice, we will notify you by email or through a notice on our website homepage. Contact Information If you have any questions or comments about this notice, our the ways in which we collect and use your personal information, your choices and rights regarding such use, or wish to exercise your rights under California law, please do not hesitate to submit a request form or by calling toll free at 844-277-9138. EFFECTIVE DATE: 1/1/20
×
My Offers
30% OFFEVERYTHING
$99 minimum purchase required
Use code 30OFF99 at checkout
Expires 12/13/20
APPLY
3 FREE SAMPLES
Enjoy 3 Free Invitation Samples
Includes Free Shipping Too!
Use code MY3FREE at checkout
APPLY
SUBSCRIBE TO
EXCLUSIVE OFFERS
Sign Up For Emails
You may withdraw your consent at any time
by following the unsubscribe link on emails.
SIGN UP
Searching for a wedding invitation coupon? We love a great deal too! We want to put money back into your wedding budget, which is why we offer an extra discount every day. Click “apply” to automatically use your selected promo code in your cart.
